<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Saqib Mir</title>
    <link>https://saqibmir1.github.io/outer-rim/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Saqib Mir</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://saqibmir1.github.io/outer-rim/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About This Rebel</title>
      <link>https://saqibmir1.github.io/outer-rim/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saqibmir1.github.io/outer-rim/pages/about/</guid>
      
      <description>Greetings, fellow sentient being from across the galaxy! I am an outrageous concoction of excessive self-consciousness and melancholic tendencies, with a dash of quirkiness and a sprinkle of oddball charm - much like a protocol droid with existential crisis subroutines.
When I&amp;rsquo;m not busy contemplating the futility of existence like a philosophical Jedi master, you can usually find me:
🛠️ Tinkering with the Force (aka Free and Open Source Software) 🐱 Studying Loth-cat behavioral patterns (binge-watching cat videos) 💻 Maintaining my personal Death Star (desktop Linux systems) 🎵 Curating the galaxy&amp;rsquo;s finest cantina music (see the music widget above) 📜 Documenting my adventures through this holocron (blog) Like Sisyphus pushing his boulder, I find meaning in the eternal struggle against proprietary software and the endless quest for the perfect .</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chat Box</title>
      <link>https://saqibmir1.github.io/outer-rim/pages/chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saqibmir1.github.io/outer-rim/pages/chat/</guid>
      
      <description>	</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holo-Contact Protocols</title>
      <link>https://saqibmir1.github.io/outer-rim/pages/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saqibmir1.github.io/outer-rim/pages/contact/</guid>
      
      <description>Establishing Communication Channels &amp;ldquo;Help me, Obi-Wan Kenobi. You&amp;rsquo;re my only hope.&amp;rdquo; - But actually, there are several ways to reach this rebel:
🛸 Primary Communication Arrays Subspace Email: The most reliable way to send transmissions across the galaxy. Response time: Usually within one parsec.
Telegram Beacon: For real-time communication when the Empire isn&amp;rsquo;t monitoring channels. Status: 24/7 operational, even during Death Star attacks.
Matrix Protocol: Encrypted rebel communications network. Currently on standby mode, but available for covert operations.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://saqibmir1.github.io/outer-rim/pages/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saqibmir1.github.io/outer-rim/pages/links/</guid>
      
      <description>Here are some links/bookmarks that i find useful or interesting Interesting Websites by Individuals Websites not about any specific topic, but included because I like their writing.
bt bikobatanari Jared White Luke Smith Manuel Moreale Webring This website is a part of blackpiratex&amp;rsquo;s webring </description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rebel Arsenal &amp; Technology</title>
      <link>https://saqibmir1.github.io/outer-rim/pages/stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saqibmir1.github.io/outer-rim/pages/stuff/</guid>
      
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Your weapons&amp;hellip; you will not need them.&amp;rdquo; - Master Yoda
Here&amp;rsquo;s my collection of digital weapons in the ongoing rebellion against proprietary tyranny and the endless quest for technological freedom.
🛠️ Active Rebel Projects SusPixels A collaborative canvas where rebels from across the galaxy can leave their mark - inspired by the legendary r/place battlegrounds.
Tech Arsenal: NestJS for command center, VanillaJS for rebel interface, PostgreSQL for archives, WebSockets for real-time coordination, Redis for hyperspeed communications Mission Status: Under Construction Hyperspace Links: Death Star Plans | Live Battleground Scroblite A real-time intelligence dashboard intercepting my musical transmissions via Last.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
